<scene name="intro" >
<!--First event-->
<event>You are slowly and carefully moving towards the front door of an abandoned army barracks. It has been a week since the outbreak of a deadly virus which has caused people to change into blood thirsty savages. You slowly open the front door and peer inside. The coast looks clear. You are hoping to find weapons and ammunition so that you and your fellow survivors can defend yourselves in the likely event of being attacked by the blood sucking mutants. There are three others with you. John O'Malley, a 50 year old investment banker from the city, Marie Smith, an 18 year old student who was until now looking forward to starting college and finally a 25 year old football player named Ben Miller. You and the three others move into the main hall and take cover behind a pillar. You check if the main hall is clear but at the very end you can see a walker drinking from a dead body. Do you try to move up the hall?</event>
<key>26</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first event-->
<event>You feel its better to take cover and see if the walker will leave. The rest of the group are getting anxious. It is not smart to hang around in the same area for too long. The walkers have a keen sense of smell and can detect humans from quite a distance. The noise of the walker seems to get louder. You take another look at the end of the hall. There are three walkers now feasting off of the body. "We have to distract them" Ben whispers. He runs out into the open and yells at the walkers. "Come get me!" The three walkers react immediately. They break into a sprint after Ben who starts to run in the opposite direction. They Gallop past the pillar you are hiding behind after Ben who tries to open a door to escape. It's locked. They pounce on Ben and dig their teeth into him. Do you try to help him?</event>
<key>11</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first event-->
<event>You give the signal to the rest to move up the hall towards the walker. You move slowly with the rest of the group and stay glued to the wall. The walkers head rarely comes up for air as he devours his victim. You get closer to the walker and suddenly he halts any movement. He looks up and his green and red eyes meet yours. The walker lets out a screech which almost deafens you. He runs straight for you. Do you try to fight him?</event>
<key>31</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first events left child-->
<event>YouDontHelp</event>
<key>6</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first events left child-->
<event>YouHelpHim</event>
<key>17</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first events right child-->
<event>YouFight</event>
<key>44</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first events right child-->
<event>YouDontFight</event>
<key>30</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
</scene>
