<scene>
<!--First event-->
<event>You seem pretty sure after reading through the notes that this is infact your work. You pull out the seat from under the desk and continue to read through the papers. It looks like you're writing a paper on genetic mutations. The books stacked on the desk are all related to this topic. As you read on it become clear to you that what you are proposing is highly unethical. You then see a photography peaking out from under a stack of notes. It is a picture of a young child with a strange deformity on its legs and arms. As you closer you can see that the child has instead of fingers and toes, he has what looks like claws. You find a number on one of the pieces of paper. Do you ring it? </event>
<answer>yes</answer>
<key>26</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<!--Left child of the first event-->
<event>You don't call the number, but instead you walk out of the room into the hall. It's a small narrow hallway with a door right across from you. You turn right and walk to the end of the hall into the kitchen. You get a waft of warm stew which has filled the air. On the cooker there is a pot with food in it. You go over and try some.</event>
<answer>no</answer>
<key>11</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<!--Right child of the first event-->
<event>You pick up the phone which is sitting on the corner of the desk. You dial the number and wait for someone to answer on the other line.
"Hello, CornerStone Technologys, this is Amy speaking, how can I help?"
You wonder about what you should say...
"Hello" the lady replies to the silence.
"Hi this is...John..John Smith..."
"Hi John Smith, how can I help you?"
"Im looking for the biotechnology lab...."</event>
<answer>yes</answer>
<key>31</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<!--Left child of the first events left child-->
<event>afternoonscene</event>
<answer>no</answer>
<key>6</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<!--Right child of the first events left child-->
<event>afternoonscene</event>
<answer>no</answer>
<key>17</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<!--Right child of the first events right child-->
<event>afternoonscene</event>
<answer>yes</answer>
<key>44</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
<!--Left child of the first events right child-->
<event>afternoonscene</event>
<answer>yes</answer>
<key>30</key>
<isScene>yes</isScene>
</scene>