<scene name="YouDontHelp" >
<!--First event-->
<event>You leave Ben and run up the hall with the rest of the group. You turn the corner and end up in a large room which looks like the canteen of the barracks. You can hear Marie sobbing behind you. "We shouldn't have left him." "He sacrificed himself to save us" John replied. "He didn't want to die" said Marie. You walk down through the canteen and come to a door. It looks like the door to the kitchen. "We shouldn't go in there." said Marie. "There could be more in there" "Ya well they could come after us when they finish with Ben!" John snapped. Marie began to cry again. Do you open the door?</event>
<key>26</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first event-->
<event>You agree with Marie. It's too risky and after all you are after weapons not food. You instead retrace your steps back through the canteen. As you walk past one of the tables, Marie's bag hits off of a cup which knocks it to the floor. The handle on the kitchen door starts to turn. Do you stick around to see what it is?</event>
<key>11</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first event-->
<event>You slowly open the door. It creaks as it opens. The lights are off and its hard to see anything. The three of you move into the kitchen. There are bodies on the floor which you are careful not to step on them    . Suddenly John lets out a scream. You turn to see Johns ankle held by a walker. He screams for help. Do you help him?</event>
<key>31</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first events left child-->
<event>You decide not to and instead you run back through the door you came in. You come to a stairs and make your way up as fast as you can. You can hear the loud and heavy steps of the walkers behind you. They are getting closer. Marie the slowest gets taken out first. Then John followed by Ben. You reach the top of the stairs where you see a large exit door which looks like it could lead out to the roof. You run for the door and try to open it. Its locked. You turn to see 20 walkers coming straight for you. They rip you to shreds.</event>
<key>6</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first events left child-->
<event>You wait with bated breath to see what comes out from behind the door. The door whips open and to your horror you see three walkers emerge from the room. They let out a screech which echoes throughout the building. They break into a sprint, running straight for you. You valiantly try to fight them but you and the others are no match for the walkers. You die in a gruesome death along with the others.</event>
<key>17</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first events right child-->
<event>You run over to John and begin to kick and stomp the walker. Another grabs you from behind and digs his teeth into your back. You can't move. The darkness drowns your sight. You were killed.</event>
<key>44</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first events right child-->
<event>You turn and run with Marie out the door at the end of the kitchen. It leads you outside. You continue to run as fast as you can but its no use. More walkers chase you and you can not out run them. They catch up to you and Marie and kill you both.</event>
<key>30</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
</scene>
