<scene name="YouHelpHim" >
<!--First event-->
<event>You put the pen knife in your pocket and drop the bag to the ground. You decide to walk deeper into the woods. The branchs and leaves crack and pop on every step. You try to remeber how you got here. You ask yourself what are you doing in the woods, but you can't answer. As you slowly move through the trees, you hear a gunshot. You try to pick up some speed but your tired legs dont move any faster. Another gunshot goes off. It's louder than before and the noise creates a buzzing in your ears. A voice shouts from behind you. As you turn to look, you are tackled to the ground. Do you reach for the pen knife?</event>
<key>26</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first event-->
<event>You panic and try to push the man off of you but you lack the strength to do so. He roars at you "Why did you kill her?". You have no idea who he is talking about. Do you respond?</event>
<key>11</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first event-->
<event>You pull out the knife and push it hard into the the persons stomach. You feel it pierce through the skin. He gasps for air. You push it further in. He stops moving. Silence fills the woods again. You pull yourself our from under him. Do you keep moving?</event>
<key>31</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>no</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first events left child-->
<event>You don't respond. The struggle continues. Another gunshot goes off. You feel a burning sensation in your belly. You have been shot.</event>
<key>6</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first events left child-->
<event>You tell him that you dont know what he is talking about. He jumps off you with his gun pointing straight at your head. He pulls the trigger. He kills you.</event>
<key>17</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
<!--Right child of the first events right child-->
<event>You go deeper into the woods.</event>
<key>44</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
<!--Left child of the first events right child-->
<event>You stay there and try to figure out who he is.</event>
<key>30</key>
<isScene>no</isScene>
<isEnding>yes</isEnding>
</scene>
